<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-09-30T14:27:10-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Cyber Offensive / Defensive Engineering</title><subtitle>Columbus' security research community</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to CO/DE!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018-10-01-introduction/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to CO/DE!" /><published>2018-09-29T05:09:13-04:00</published><updated>2018-09-29T05:09:13-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/introduction</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018-10-01-introduction/">&lt;p&gt;CO/DE is the realization of a vision many years in the making. The people working behind the scenes to make CO/DE possible (include you) have worked tirelessly in persuit of excelllence in their specializations, mentoring others in their organizations, and learning from their peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But our peers exist beyond the walls and conference calls of our organizations - they exist all over our city and they’re extremely talented. Containing that talent within the confines of individual organizations is a great disservice to us all. And while many of us are contractually obligated to protect IP and sensitive information, we are in no such obligation to keep our talents and passion for cybersecurity a secret.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mission of CO/DE is to strengthen Columbus Ohio’s cybersecurity community through technical knowledge sharing and collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means working together to share our knowledge for the benefit of others. Whether you’re a student interested cybersecurity, a seasoned professional, or looking to make the trasition from another field, CO/DE is for you. Cybersecurity is a large field with many specializations, so it’s common to have people extremely well versed in offensive topics without truly understanding the defensive side and vice versa. CO/DE aims to fill those gaps and expose members to various aspects of our craft to strengthen the talent here in Columbus, Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CO/DE is still in its infancy and highly dependent on local companies for workshop space. We’re working with local cybersecurity talent and organizations to secure space, instructors, and mentors. If you would like to help us out, please contact us at contact@hackingwithcode.io.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="announcements" /><summary type="html">CO/DE is the realization of a vision many years in the making. The people working behind the scenes to make CO/DE possible (include you) have worked tirelessly in persuit of excelllence in their specializations, mentoring others in their organizations, and learning from their peers.</summary></entry></feed>